Ko Mun-yeong.
Run.
- It's okay, Ko Mun-yeong.
- Run...
- Please run. Go!
- It was just a dream.
Please run. Go!
Get out at once!
Get lost.
Leave at once.
Okay, I won't leave.
Why are you here?
- You were burning up all night.
- So?
You laid me down and played doctor?
Just stay in bed.
I'll drop Sang-tae off at his work
and pick up medicine.
I didn't do anything wrong.
That woman kept acting
as if she were my mom,
so I told her that my mom died.
That's all.
Right, okay.
CHAPTER 7
THE CHEERFUL DOG
Seongjin, Seongjin... Seongjin Plaza.
Michuri Public Health Center.
Hiking... Hiking Trail Entrance.
Oeryong Bridge.
Stop memorizing that.
Go wash up, Sang-tae.
I'll take you to Jae-su's restaurant.
Let's head out together.
I can go on my own. On my own.
I know.
But I have to go downtown too.
You don't have to go
to the hospital today?
I'm going to
skip work today.
- You can't leave like this.
- Rewind a little.
Okay.
The patient may go through conversion
and stop deluding herself,
so let's keep an eye on her
and see what happens.
- Yes, sir.
Sir.
I think you have to take this up
with Ms. Ko Mun-yeong as well.
First, let's find out
what she said to the patient.
I bet she said something like,
"Your daughter is dead."
So she fainted from the emotional shock.
How would Ms. Ko know about that?
Maybe Mr. Moon told her.
- They're close, you know.
- No, they're not.
You all know that he'd never disclose
any patient information.
Anyway, we've been having problems nonstop
ever since Ms. Ko started coming
to our hospital.
We need to do something about this.
Yes.
I agree.
Me too.
Could you please stop scraping off
your dandruff and make a decision?
Let's put her fairy tale class on pause
until we find out what really happened.
- Okay.
Would that be all?
Tell Mr. Moon
that I'd like to speak with him.
He didn't come in today.
He called earlier and said
that something came up at home.
Oh, really?
Sang-tae, how do you feel
about quitting the job
at Jae-su's restaurant?
You've been doing so many things
ever since we moved here.
Drawing the mural at the hospital
and selling pizza at Jae-su's restaurant.
When you start
working on the illustrations...
You'll be too busy.
Being busy isn't a bad thing.
Right, it's not a bad thing.
But if you're too busy,
you might fall ill.
- You may ache all over--
- Like a dog.
What?
You whimper like a dog at night
when you're ill.
I don't do that, but you always
whimper like a dog when you sleep.
Hello.
What? I do that?
That's odd.
I'm not ill.
I no longer work multiple jobs,
so I feel perfectly fine.
It's because your heart is aching.
"Your body is honest.
When you're in physical pain, you cry.
But the heart is a liar.
It stays quiet even when it's hurting.
Then when you're asleep,
you finally weep and whimper like a dog."
You like this book that much?
Yes, The Cheerful Dog by Ms. Ko Mun-yeong.
"Written by Ko Mun-yeong.
Once upon a time..."
Oh, we're not open yet...
You jerk! You moved in with her
without discussing it with me.
Did you think I'd be happy to--
Hello?
Yes.
Let's talk later.
- Right.
- Later? When?
Hey! I'll be waiting, okay? Hey!
- Hi, Jae-su.
- Goodness!
Jeez. Hi, Sang-tae.
She's not feeling well.
Come on. When did she start
feeling unwell? And what are the symptoms?
I need details!
She's not answering my calls.
I'm getting a bad feeling.
- I was worried all night--
- I'll tell her to give you a call.
I have to go.
GEUKJIN PHARMACY
I can't believe
he hung up on me like that.
Gosh, that heartless prick.
Right?
He would be way more attractive
if he was more relaxed.
He's too uptight. What a shame.
But physically, he's totally my type.
You have to tiptoe around me
every single day,
yet you're still so dull-witted.
How's that possible?
Right? Had I been quick-witted,
I wouldn't have trusted you
and come all the way here.
Sorry about that.
It's all my fault.
I have to go check in on Mun-yeong.
Settle up with this
and get a latte or something
at a cafe somewhere.
See you later, sir!
That son of a bitch.
Maybe I should side with Ko Mun-young.
He that would eat the fruit
must climb the tree.
Mamma mia!
MR. LEE
Long hair suits you
because you take after me.
Never cut your hair short.
But I'm tired of it.
You have to listen to Mom, right?
Answer me.
Answer me!
Yes,
Mom.
Please...
Save me!
Mun-yeong.
Are you okay?
I want to cut it,
but I just can't.
Cut what?
My mom.
Did you get sleep paralysis again
because of that hallucination?
Since when?
When did you start
experiencing them again?
The first day back here.
You can't stay here.
I'm taking you back to Seoul now.
I'm warning you.
Do not touch any of my stuff.
Then let me warn you as well!
I'm going to knock you out if I must,
so don't stop me.
I know that you'll be destroyed
if those hallucinations
start haunting you again.
So I absolutely cannot let you stay here.
I've had a bad feeling ever since
you talked about those red shoes
and moved here with that caregiver guy.
You two should've never gotten involved--
I've known you for ten years.
I at least know this much.
- Follow me.
- Let go!
Come with me!
- Come on.
Let go of my hand.
Do you have a death wish?
Sure, I'll die so you can live.
And you must leave this house to live.
Come on. Let's go.
- Jeez.
- I'm not leaving.
- Let go.
- I won't even budge.
You have to leave. Let go already.
What the hell are you doing?
You stay out of this.
Mun-yeong and I...
Will you get off me?
Well...
I'm taking her.
You should pack up
and get out of this place too. Hurry!
Let's go, Mun-yeong.
Did you just hit me?
- Kick him out at once.
- Hey.
Why are you acting all weak?
Dragging her against her will
is considered violence.
What?
You used it first,
so I can use it too, right?
Hey, that hurts!
Hey, wait!
Mun-yeong.
Hey, that guy doesn't know much about you!
I'm the only one who can
protect and look after you.
Mun-yeong?
Damn it!
Keep the door locked
when you're here alone.
- If anyone can--
- Do you think someone will harm me?
Come on. Me?
It'll probably be the other way around.
Still, keep it locked.
You said scary things can happen
when you let your guard down.
Take this fever reducer.
If I took crap like this
every single time I need to cool down,
I'd already be a junkie.
This won't cool me down.
Then get some fresh air.
I like what you prescribed me.
- Where do you want to go?
- A motel.
What do you want to eat?
You.
Are you going to keep this up?
Okay, fine. I'll follow
my doctor's instructions today.
What will you feed me?
Thank you. Enjoy.
This looks good.
Sang-tae.
No, don't say that. You have to say
"come on" to call me over.
When someone says "later,"
what does it actually mean?
Sometime before you die.
What? Before you die?
Yes.
No way.
We've known each other for so long.
He'd never do that to me.
For how long? How much?
1,000 won? 2,000 won?
I met you and Gang-tae
when I was only 16.
At Jae-su's Fried Chicken.
That's right.
My parents had a fried chicken place,
and Gang-tae worked there part-time
and lived with us.
I'm a year older than him,
but he never treated me as such.
And he always gave you all the drumsticks.
I only eat drumsticks.
I envied you.
I wished I'd also had
a little brother like Gang-tae.
So one day, I said to him, "Think of me
as your brother, you little prick."
Then he said,
"I don't need another brother."
- I'm his real brother.
- That was when I realized this.
"He needs a friend, not another brother."
I need a friend too.
It's good.
I guess what I needed was food,
not medicine.
This is awakening my ferociousness.
I feel much better now.
- It's not cooked yet.
- It's okay.
I have a lot of internal heat.
I can't control myself around food.
I'm hungry no matter how much I eat.
Is it because I'm an empty can?
I'm sorry.
I was just
talking nonsense then.
- It's true though.
- No.
You're not an empty can.
Then what am I?
Well...
A thug?
Eat up. It'll burn.
As you may already know,
I only sold chicken after that.
Fried, steamed, sweet and sour,
drumsticks, and even chicken feet.
- Why do you think I did that?
- Chicken head.
That's the only part you didn't sell.
The chicken head.
That's right.
- The chicken head isn't sellable.
- That's right.
You know, I didn't want to sell chicken.
I was even sick of the smell.
But it was the only kind of business
I could open and close quickly.
Because I didn't know
when my friend had to move again,
I kept selling chicken.
But this time, it felt different.
I felt that he might settle down
in Seongjin City.
So I put together all the money I had
and even took out a loan
to finally open a different kind
of business. No more chicken.
But he...
He left me.
Why?
Because he likes
that lunatic Ko Mun-yeong
more than me, his friend of 15 years.
- No, that's not why.
- That is why!
It was because of me.
Gang-tae followed me
because of my contract with her.
It's like a BOGO deal.
Don't trust Gang-tae too much.
You might end up like me.
Like you?
Like the dog that chased the chicken.
A dog?
A dog!
That was loud. I'm sorry. That was loud.
- Hello, Mr. Moon.
- Hello!
By the way, why aren't you eating?
You're just feeding me.
I'm not really hungry.
Have you ever slept with a woman?
- Never?
- Why are you suddenly talking nonsense?
You seem to have no desires whatsoever.
You don't want to eat, have,
or do anything.
You always look apathetic.
- I'm not apathetic.
- Then what?
I'm just suppressing myself.
Why?
You do everything you want to do,
but that's not the case for most people.
Don't suppress yourself.
It shouldn't be that hard.
Your safety pin...
Shall I pull it for you?
I'm curious
to see what will happen
if you don't suppress yourself.
Hey, Byeol.
Patient Park Ji-hwan
falls from his bed easily,
so make sure you help him if he needs
to go to the bathroom at night.
I've already told Mr. O Cha-yong
everything he needs to know.
Both of you should check on him
when doing your rounds.
Okay, got it.
And as for patient Kim Jeong-mi's
depression...
Just a second.
What's up? Sang-tae is here.
He's chatting with the employee
from Ko Mun-yeong's publishing company.
It's pissing me off.
Who is it?
It's nothing.
- Where were we?
- Patient Kim Jeong-mi.
That was a lengthy explanation.
Let me sum it up for you.
If Mr. Lee Sang-in's muse is
Ms. Ko Mun-yeong,
then as the art director,
I get inspiration from you.
You're my muse.
That was what I was trying to say.
I see.
That's why
I brought some illustrations
you can refer to
while working on Ms. Ko's next book--
- Where are you going?
- I'm leaving for the day.
It's rude to talk about irrelevant work
at someone else's workplace.
Complete nonsense.
Let's... Let's talk about it later.
"Later" means sometime before you die.
Jae-su, this is for you.
- Bye, Sang-tae.
- Bye!
What did he draw?
The dog that chased the chicken.
Why are we walking?
What?
It's nice to walk and enjoy the scenery.
It helps you clear your mind
and lifts your spirits.
Really? All I can think is that
my legs hurt and it's a waste of time.
- Then shall we--
- Will you carry me?
What?
I wonder if Sang-tae is on his way home.
I guess he's fine on his own.
No! Jeez.
So you should just focus on me.
Okay, give it back.
Come on. Give it back.
Stop it.
Are you
holding me in your arms now?
- Hey, Ju-ri.
- Hey.
Ko Mun-yeong?
My daring roommate
is in an awkward situation now,
so I'm answering his phone. What's up?
Well, he didn't come into work today.
He took the day off to hang out with me.
Bye.
You didn't go to work
because you were worried about me?
And you took me out on a date
to help me cool off?
Who said this was a date?
What was this, then?
Are you flirting with me?
Or are you feeling it out?
Are you just testing the waters?
Or are you playing me?
Fine.
Let's date.
"Get lost."
- What?
- "Get lost."
Do you know how many times
you've said that to me?
Even last night. And that day too.
So what?
But last night, it sounded like
you were begging me not to leave.
Last time, I ran away.
But today,
I thought I should stay with you.
That's all it meant.
Ko Mun-yeong, you heartless woman.
All my organs are rotting
because of the stress from
looking after you for the past ten years.
How could you gang up on me
with that caregiver you just met
and kick me out? Just how?
Fine, you two heartless jerks
can live happily ever after.
I'm going to find the kindest
and sweetest woman on earth and--
Shit!
You're so loud. Damn it!
Unrequited love is so hard. I give up!
I guess you've never seen a woman
who's heartbroken by unrequited love.
Hey, Jae-su.
Why
can't it be me?
Why that bitch?
I can
swear too.
And I can also
throw temper tantrums and smash things.
I can
stop acting nice all the time.
And I can
be a bitch too.
Gosh, no. Not everyone can be a bitch.
Who are you?
Why cut me off?
I'm not a weirdo.
I'm...
the CEO of SangSangESang Publishers.
My name is Lee Sang-in.
CEO LEE SANG-IN
So it's all your fault.
Don't cry.
Do you know me?
You should've talked Ko Mun-yeong
out of it.
Then she wouldn't have moved here,
and those two would've never met.
Then I wouldn't have ended up like this.
This is all on you.
CEO Lee Sang-in.
It's all your fault.
Hold on, this voice...
Are you...
Hello?
My tears.
Mr. Lee. I'm Nam Ju-ri,
a nurse at OK Psychiatric Hospital.
Nurse Nam Ju-ri?
Last time, I ran away.
But today,
I thought I should stay with you.
What is it?
Nothing.
I had a nightmare last night.
My nightmares are always about my mom.
And when I wake up from the dream,
I always feel like shit.
But today,
I don't feel so shitty.
OK PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
But why? Just why?
Why are they getting rid of the class?
I liked her class because it was always
like a big smack in the head.
I knew they'd get rid of it.
I always questioned her state of mind,
and she had a bad attitude.
- Are you a school superintendent?
- I'm just a super old man, you punk!
Stop hitting me in the head, will you?
You said you like a big smack in the head.
I did all the homework.
They can't get rid of this class.
I was confident
that she'd compliment me this time.
Are you possessed by a spirit
who wants to brag about doing homework?
Why cry so early in the morning?
You're ruining my day.
Why must you say such mean things
to A-reum so early in the morning?
You two...
Are you seeing each other or something?
Let's go, A-reum. Just ignore her.
I think they'll cause trouble
sooner or later.
Did you eat?
I had a fried egg, cubed radish kimchi,
three sausages, and soybean paste stew.
What are you doing right now?
I'm just sitting down.
What about Ms. Ko?
She's just sitting down.
What?
- Sang-tae.
- Yes?
- Let's just have fun today.
- Okay.
Come in.
I heard you asked for me yesterday.
Yes, there's something I want to ask you.
Does Ms. Ko have a boyfriend?
Well, I'm not sure.
I have a son. I had him pretty late.
Anyway, I'd like to introduce him to her.
Don't worry. He takes after his mom,
so he looks nothing like me.
What do you say? Should I do it or not?
Why are you asking me?
Because you live with her.
Let's come separately next time.
People will get the wrong idea.
When are you done?
Let's go home together. I'll wait.
Does your car run on gasoline or diesel?
I've been psychoanalyzing people
for so long
that I can tell what their stories are
just by looking in their eyes.
Why didn't you come in yesterday?
I wasn't feeling well.
You mean, Ms. Ko wasn't feeling well?
Yes.
Ms. Sun Byeol said
Ms. Kang Eun-ja acted like she was her mom
and bugged her. Is that why?
It seemed like Ms. Ko
thought she was actually her mother
for a moment.
THE MURDER OF THE WITCH OF THE WEST
WRITTEN BY DO HUI-JAE
Ms. Ko's mother
is the writer, Do Hui-jae.
The day she finished the last book
of her fiction series,
she vanished without a trace.
Then she was registered as deceased
five years after she disappeared.
THE MURDER OF THE WITCH OF THE WEST
You're always one step late.
Some believed that she was still alive.
There were a lot of rumors back then.
Could she be alive?
Then she wouldn't have kept
her readers waiting for almost 20 years,
knowing how much they want
to find out what ends up happening
to the Witch of the West.
My nightmares are always about my mom.
It must've been a big shock to Ms. Ko.
And I'm sure she misses her a lot.
Maybe that's why she mistook
someone else for her mother.
But what if she doesn't miss her?
What if she fears her?
COUNSELLING NOTE
PATIENT NAME KO DAE-HWAN
HE GAVE SHORT, SIMPLE ANSWERS BUT DIDN'T
TRY TO AVOID ANSWERING THE QUESTIONS
My wife?
She was incredibly intelligent
and elegant.
She loved our daughter very much.
Maybe too much.
Every night, she sang
Oh My Darling, Clementine as a lullaby.
I wonder
if she knew
the true meaning behind the song.
KO MUN-YEONG'S FAIRY TALE CLASS
PUT ON PAUSE TEMPORARILY
- Ms. Park.
- What's the matter?
Are you sad
that her class is put on pause?
No.
I think the patients are sad about it.
They found the class
different and interesting.
It is interesting.
You should check out her books
when you have some time.
No, I wouldn't be able
to relate to those stories.
I like cruel and foolish love stories
or horror novels.
I'll take some water to the padded room.
All right. Thanks.
Take good care of the patient.
Would you like some water?
Well...
About your daughter.
You said you'd like me to meet her.
Next time she visits you, I will--
My daughter...
is dead.
Mom.
How are you going to meet a dead girl?
Even I can't meet her.
Dr. Kwon!
Darn it.
Dr. Kwon, Ms. Kang Eun-ja is showing
conversion symptoms.
What? Is she in the padded room?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
This shawl...
It's very expensive.
It's worth more than
hundreds of millions of won.
I had never received
something so expensive in my entire life.
We barely managed to afford a living.
But she spent her entire paycheck
to buy me
this shawl
for my birthday.
How much is this?
How many zeros are there?
Goodness! Go and get a refund right now!
I got so furious and angry.
So I slapped her really hard on her back.
Do you think somebody like me
deserves something this expensive?
I'm so sick
and tired of you being like this.
I don't remember much.
But I remember saying this.
I don't need
an immature daughter like you!
I ended up telling her that I don't need
a daughter like her.
If I had known
she was going to die like that,
I never would've
said something so harsh.
Never.
- Gang-tae.
- Yes?
You need to stay by your brother's side
until the day you die.
That's why
I gave birth to you.
Why in the world did I say that to her?
I'm such an idiot.
Why do you look so sad?
You're making it hard for me to get angry.
You should also lie down.
Jae-su.
Yes?
Do you think
my mom also feels sorry
for how she treated me?
Do you think
she regrets it?
Is that what you want?
Yes.
No.
Ma'am, why were you so mean to Gang-tae?
Sang-tae wasn't your only son!
I know he's sick, but still!
Why did you discriminate Gang-tae
and prevent him from growing up properly?
You're crazy.
You just wait 60 years.
Once I meet you up there, I'm going to--
What are you going to do?
My goodness.
All mothers are sinners.
But even so, cut your mother some slack.
Do you think it was easy for a woman
to raise kids without a husband back then?
My goodness.
I only have a daughter,
but even I wanted to run away at times.
But your mother
successfully raised two boys.
On top of that, Sang-tae is one of a kind.
You've been taking care of your brother,
so I'm sure you know
how hard it must've been for her.
Cheers to us. This is for you up there.
My goodness, you're unbelievable.
Do you feel better now?
- Gang-tae came by and left just now.
- Why? Was he alone? What did he say?
If you like him so much,
why did you come home
on some other guy's back last night?
Someone carried me home? Really?
You know what? It's better not to know.
Just don't bother remembering anything.
That'd be best.
CEO LEE SANG-IN
I'm the CEO of SangSangESang Publishers.
- Mr. Lee.
- Yes?
I want you to fix this!
I must've lost my mind.
Where are you? When are you coming?
Hurry up and come home. I'm bored.
Why are you ignoring me?
Are you kidding me?
WATE.
WIAT.
WAIT.
Why are you so late?
- Why were you sleeping here?
- You told me to wait. Damn it.
Did you drink?
With whom?
That two-faced bitch?
No, not her.
I drank with Jo Jae-su,
a chicken farm owner's son,
and a live-in cook
who's over 60 years old.
Did you meet people from online?
"Meet people from online"?
You're drunk.
I was drunk,
but the cab driver told me
he doesn't come here at night
because this place is scary
and brings bad luck,
and he told me to get out of the cab.
So I walked all the way here,
and I'm almost sober now.
Then let's drink some more.
No, forget it. This is
just the right amount of tipsiness.
I want to drink.
No, you can't.
You never do things in moderation.
If both of us end up getting drunk,
it'll be bad.
Why?
Are you scared I might come onto you?
- Stop acting up.
- Did you just hit me?
You hurt me with a knife.
You have good comebacks when you're drunk.
I want to pull out your safety pin.
Close your eyes.
Why?
Just close your eyes.
You're so cliché.
Here. Open your eyes.
What is this piece of crap?
A nightmare catcher.
If you sleep with this in your hand,
it collects your nightmares in its basket
and eats it up overnight.
Then you'll be able to sleep comfortably.
How childish.
I brought it from home today.
- It used to be my brother's.
- What? It's used?
I made it myself.
If it's handmade, I guess it's worth it.
This guy's name is Mang-tae.
Don't tell me you named it Mang-tae
because you're Gang-tae,
and your brother is Sang-tae.
The three of us
are brothers.
Unbelievable.
To be honest,
my brother also has nightmares
just like you.
He's been having nightmares
ever since our mom passed away.
My brother felt tormented,
but there was nothing I could do.
All I could do
was make him this silly doll.
Well, it's kind of cute
now that I take a close look at it.
- Do you want it?
- Yes, I want it.
Okay.
Good night.
Mang-tae.
Sang-tae.
Are you sleeping?
Are you really sleeping?
Gosh, you reek of alcohol.
I'm... I'm so upset.
My gosh, you... You stink.
You reek of alcohol.
Sang-tae, let's have jjamppong someday
at that place we used to go with Mom.
- It's at the entrance of the market.
- Yes.
You used to love the jjamppong there.
No, you... You were the one who loved it.
No, you always--
"It has chili pepper and mussels inside.
The broth tastes amazing.
I want to have it every day, Mom."
You told her that.
That's why she bought us that jjamppong
every time the market opened.
"It's spicy but tasty."
Sang-tae, jjamppong is spicy but tasty.
It makes me want to eat it again.
HARIMGAK
The jjamppong is here.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Here. Eat up.
What about you, Mom?
I'm not hungry.
Eat up.
It's... It's spicy.
- Is it spicy? Drink some water.
- It's spicy.
It's spicy.
My gosh, it's pouring.
You'll catch a cold. Are you okay?
Gang-tae, what are you doing?
- Gang-tae, get over here. It's raining.
- Gang-tae, get over here.
Come on.
Look at you. You're all wet.
Let's go home and get you changed.
Be careful.
Gang-tae, should we
eat jjamppong again tomorrow?
"Jjamppong"?
It's hard to lose five kilograms.
But I tried so hard.
I didn't drink Coke or eat rice,
and I lost five kilograms.
I lost five kilograms. It was amazing.
We... We need to listen to our mom.
We need to listen to our mom.
We need to listen to our mom
in order to be a good person.
Our mom knows everything.
Our mom knows... She knows everything.
Don't catch a cold. Don't drink Coke.
My adorable son.
I'm so sorry for everything.
Sang-tae.
Yes?
I miss Mom.
Yes.
I want jjamppong, too.
I want jjamppong every single day.
OK PSYCHIATRIC HOSPITAL
Everyone badmouths you
saying you made Ms. Kang Eun-ja collapse.
But I never badmouthed you.
To be honest, that woman isn't sane.
She always wears the shawl she got
from her late daughter
and pretends like she's rich.
- That darn geezer. Move.
- I really don't think--
Ms. Ko.
- She hit me again.
- Darn it.
Oh, gosh.
Emergency.
We have a situation. What should we do?
- What is it?
- What's wrong?
Will you please be quiet?
Be silent.
Are you trying to agitate the patients?
Be careful when you use
the word "emergency."
Ms. Ko is here. I think she came
not knowing her class got canceled.
She had this look on her face
and went to find the director.
- Didn't you call her?
- Didn't you?
Why didn't you?
- What?
- You guys are close.
No, they're not!
Wait. Wait a minute.
Does that mean
no one called and told Ms. Ko
that her fairy tale class got canceled?
What's wrong with you?
She found out through the notice board.
She must be furious right now.
I'll go find her.
I used to run marathons when I was young.
But one day, my knees got infected.
I should've gotten some rest,
but I just ran a marathon again.
In the end, my cartilage got ruined,
and I ended up with metal pins.
Now, it's hard for me
to even walk properly.
Don't make the same mistake I did
and try to run when you can't even walk.
When you're tired, get some rest.
When you're sad, go ahead and cry.
It's okay to take a break.
Then one day,
there will surely come a day
when you'll be able to run again.
I bet your daughter is cheering you on.
That darn geezer. How dare he cancel
my class without telling me?
There he is.
Darn, did he take drugs or something?
Why is he so fast?
Ms. Ko!
Wait here for a second.
Let me take you back to your room.
I'm sorry.
I'm guessing I put you
in a difficult position.
You didn't just put me
I got fired.
Hey.
How will you compensate for this?
This is expensive.
- I want it.
- But that's...
Let me have this.
You told me you're sorry.
Then you should compensate for the damage.
That's what you call a sincere apology.
Give it back.
Take it.
I've had it for more than enough.
Mr. Moon.
Yes?
The burden is finally gone.
Isn't it hot?
I bet your neck is sweating.
If you want to be fashionable,
you must be uncomfortable and stubborn.
My brother is immersed
in one of your books these days.
I know.
The Cheerful Dog.
"Once upon a time,
there lived a dog that was
very good at hiding his emotions.
The dog was tied beneath a shade tree.
He always wagged his tail and acted cute.
So he got the name, "The Cheerful Dog,"
because he was as cheerful as springtime.
The dog always had lots of fun
with the village kids during the day.
But every night,
he'd moan and whine
when no one was around.
That's because
he wanted to cut off the leash
and freely run around
out in the spring field.
However, he couldn't.
And that's why he cried every night.
Every single night.
One day,
a voice inside him asked the Cheerful Dog.
'Hey, why don't you just cut off the leash
and run away?'
And this is what the Cheerful Dog said..."
"I've been tied up for way too long.
So I forgot how to cut myself free."
You did great, Mun-yeong.
What did I do?
You helped her cut herself free.
You will
end up like your mother.
You won't be able to escape.
No.
I'm different.
Your...
- Your hair--
- I...
cut off my leash.
PATIENT ROOM 201-208
It's all done.
How do I look?
You look pretty.
SPECIAL THANKS TO BAE HAE-SUN
FOR MAKING A GUEST APPEARANCE
I'm very pretty.
I'm just like your brother.
Longer hair suits you better.
Why did she cut it? Why?
Chew on this.
Why do you think she lied?
It seems like something strange
is happening at our hospital.
That woman
is dead.
But she's here.
Safety pin and bomb.
You're patient, and I'm volatile.
Could you take a photo of us?
According to Mr. Lee, I sell one more book
every time I smile at a fan.
An author only needs to write well.
She's not a celebrity.
- Are you jealous?
- Jealous, my ass.
"Offer"?
But if I give all my stuff to people
who need them,
what will I have left?
Subtitle translation by Ja-won Lee